# MAYANK SABHARWAL

### FULL STACK DEVELOPER



mayanksabharwal8@gmail.com

Mouse no. 586/3, Faridabad

### **PROFILE**

I am a qualified and intermediate full stack developer with one year and eight months of experience in website development and web applications. With my strong creative and logical skills i like to enhance the UI/UX of the project. Team player with an eye for detail.

### SKILLS

### **FRONTEND**

- HTML 5 + Css 3
- JS + Jquery + Ajax
- React is
- Angular js
- Bootstrap 5.1
- Tailwind Css

#### BACKEND

- PHP
- Laravel FrameWork (MVC MODEL)
- Mysql Database
- Node is with Mongo DB
- Express Js

# EDUCATION

#### SECONDARY SCHOOL

Nav Jiwan Public School 2015 - 2017

#### **BACHELORS OF TECHNOLOGY**

Chandigarh Engineering College 2017 - 2021

### EXPERIENCE

#### SHADE MARKETING AND PR AGENCY

Workholic and a great company

Aug 2021 - Present

#### **ROLE: FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

Office Projects

- E-commerce website development with database administration( thedevy.com)(organicdukan.in)
- B2B website development with database administration
- B2C website development with database administration
- Static website development
- Landing Pages
- Web application of service management system(www.gtlkailash.com)
- Team Leading of major project development

#### **DUCAT INDIA IT TRAINING COMPANY**

Wonderful IT training company

May 2022 - Present

### **ROLE: MEAN + MERN INTERN**

Internship Projects

- Static 6 pages website using Angular is with CRUD operation
- Static 6 pages website using React is with CRUD operation
- Form validation and submition using javascript and ajax

# HOBBIES

- Love to listen music
- Love to create acrylic paintings
- Love to read self-improvement books
- Love to swim a lot

# STRENGTHS

- Passionate to learn new skill everyday
- Humble with everyone
- Brave
- Determined
- Idealistic

### WEAKNESS

Perfectionism

#### **P.B AND SONS**

Website Development April 2020 - Aug 2021

#### **ROLE: WEB DEVELOPER**

- Ecommerce Website
- · Landing Pages Using HTML, CSS

#### **DUCAT INDIA IT TRAINING COMPANY**

Wonderful IT training company

May 2019 - July 2019

**ROLE: C&C++ INTERN** 

- ATM machine software using oops concept
- Student Management System using oops concept

### **PROJECTS**

#### Personal

- School Management System using PHP, Bootstrap 5.1 and Mysql with administration
- Record management system using PHP, Bootstrap 5.1 and Mysql with administration (https://rkjagatkalyan.in/) (CRUD operation)
- Service management system using PHP, Bootstrap 5.1 and Mysql with administration (CRUD operation)
- Calculator using C & C++
- E-commerce web application (dkssolar.com)
- E-commerce web application (sparevillage.com)